How to make a zip-up puller
Now open CLO
Today I will explain how to make a zip-up puller
In the previous tutorial video
It is to make a zip-up puller
Then stick it as an accessory on the clothes
Can't really pull the zip-up puller
In our new version
We can easily define the zip-up puller as a zip-up puller
It can achieve a more realistic pull effect
Now let's make a zip-up puller like this
There is a reference picture of a zip-up puller in your material
This is a zip-up puller we are going to make today
First, let's make a zip-up puller
Find the zip-up tool in the 2D window
Use the default size of 500mm x 500mm
Click OK
Then we will add the reference picture of the zip-up puller as a sticker
This is the zip-up puller we are going to make today
Then
We will adjust the transparency of the sticker a little bit
To make it easier for us to draw the outline and the outline of the inner line
Then we need to use the inner line
To draw its outline
Then you can see our reference picture of this zip-up puller
Its zip-up puller and its main body
The thickness is different
So
We need to make the zip-up puller thinner
The main body is a little bit thicker
So we need to make it into two panels
And set the thickness of the zip-up puller to it
We are now using the multi-sided line tool
First, draw the outline of this zip-up puller
Make it Sommer
Focus the pace using this palette tool
Press CTRL
To design the curve of the zip-up puller
Choose Line
Here we use geometry of this zip-up puller
Next, let's draw the curve inside.
We can adjust the position of the curve point
with the help of a ruler.
Slightly adjust the curve of the curve point.
Because the size of the curve is relatively small,
there may be some uneven edges.
We need to make some minor adjustments to it.
If we want to move the straight line point,
just press the D on the keyboard,
drag the straight line point,
and press the D on the keyboard.
After the adjustment is almost done,
we can directly select its outline.
Just cut it off directly with the right button.
Because the particle diameter of the current one is 20,
so the pattern that is drawn now
is a triangular grid.
Adjust the example of this pattern to 1.
Then let's go to the main body of the drawing.
Use the internal multidirectional line tool
to draw the main body of the drawing.
Press the Shift key to make it a trajectory.
Let's make this line more smooth.
Then we can adjust the curve of the curve point.
Let's make a closed pattern.
Then we can adjust the inner outline.
This inner line can be deleted
Then we right-click to select Cut
We don't need this big board
Can delete it
Next, we will turn the outline line inside it into a hole
Including the pull ring also needs to be converted into a hole
Then we can delete all its stickers
Use the adjustment sticker tool
Then delete the stickers on these boards
Finally, we can adjust the curve
We can see that the main body of the puller is different from the back of the puller
So we choose the main body of the puller
Increase its rendering thickness to 4
And we can adjust its curve
Its pull ring is the same
We can increase its rendering thickness by 1 mm
The curve is adjusted to 25%
Then we can delete all its stickers
Select all the elements
And then we can move the puller
And we can choose the size of the puller
We can change the size of the puller
And we can see the result of the puller
Next, I will teach you how to make this kind of logo with a three-dimensional metal carving.
We need to use a sticker to make this effect.
Before making it, we need to prepare an image of this effect.
There is also an image of the texture of the sticker.
The most important thing is this line drawing.
This is the key to make our logo present the three-dimensional metal carving effect.
We find the sticker option in the object window.
Then we drag the texture of the sticker in.
Then drag the texture of the texture in.
Add this sticker to our template.
This sticker is relatively large.
And we need to adjust its angle.
Adjust to 90 degrees.
Then we need to adjust its size.
When adjusting the size, right-click to enter its size.
I entered 4.5 mm.
Click OK.
Now our sticker is added.
But in fact, we don't need this texture.
We only need the effect of its line drawing.
Then how should we operate?
Select this sticker in the object window.
Adjust its shadow intensity to 50.
Remember to fill the color.
Then adjust the shadow brightness to 50.
Adjust the shadow intensity to negative 50.
Adjust the shadow brightness to 50.
Now we keep the auto effect of the line drawing.
The texture is processed to the brightest and whitest effect.
Then we can enhance the strength of the line drawing.
And modify the texture of the sticker to metal.
Finally, we get the metal effect.
And the effect of the logo with the auto effect.
Now we have finished making the puller with the template.
Next, we need to export OBJ.
Before exporting OBJ, we need to pre-select.
Pre-select all the templates.
Then right-click in the 3D window.
Choose to move to the ground center.
Then we need to use the positioning tool.
Drag it to the bottom of the ground.
We need to let the ground line pass through the middle of the puller.
This step is more important.
This step determines that we will define the template as a puller.
The puller is in the position of the puller head.
We need to put all the pullers in this position.
The hole passes through the ground line.
Then select the file.
Select export.
Select OBJ.
Name it puller1.
Then click save.
What we need to pay attention to is.
We need to select all the templates.
And select all the stickers and accessories.
More targets.
Select the latter.
Select the internal shape.
Save with the document.
Click confirm.
Open the project file that needs to replace the puller.
Let's open the file that we just saved.
Find the compression bag.
Unzip the compression bag.
We can see here.
There is an OBJ file.
Then we go back to the cloud.
In the top menu bar.
Find the material.
Then we find the puller.
There is a self-defined OBJ at the bottom of the puller.
Type select puller.
The name can be self-defined.
Click the button at the back of the OBJ file.
Click the button.
Select the OBJ file that has just been unzipped.
Select open.
This file is added in.
And you can check it in the preview.
Click confirm.
There will be a pop-up window.
Now let's click this puller.
In the puller here.
You can see the puller preset we just created.
You can see that this puller is relatively large.
So when we just type in.
You need to adjust its size.
I'm going to type in again now.
Select material.
Puller self-defined OBJ.
In the proportion here.
We should choose a smaller proportion.
Select this OBJ file.
We can adjust the proportion to 40%.
Then click confirm.
Again created this puller preset.
Select the second.
Now it is a suitable size.
We can adjust its slanting angle.
Then modify its material type.
Now this self-defined puller is made.
And it retains the effect of the three-dimensional logo.
The above is the self-defined puller tutorial.
The bottom is the self-defined puller.
We can adjust the length.
Then we can adjust the length.
And then we can adjust the width.
For this, we can change the width.
So we can adjust the length.